{
    "id": "4470390e8b73400db31b8ef168302dc3",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I may be blunt …………………… at least I am honest.",
            "description": "We use but to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is beautiful …………………. she squints a little.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "however",
                "even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………….. tired that he could barely stand.",
            "description": "The conjunction so...that... shows cause and effect. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You will get the award ……………………… you deserve it.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not get the job ………………….. you succeed in the interview.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if not. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… she is of noble birth, she is not rich.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. there is life, there is hope.",
            "description": "All of these can be used here with slightly different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Since",
                "While",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… you have apologized, I will not sack you.",
            "description": "All of these words indicate the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "As",
                "Because",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. he was the most deserving candidate, they appointed him.",
            "description": "Since can indicate the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "Though",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Generally speaking, the houses in ……………………… the Burmese live are made of bamboo.",
            "description": "In which can mean where. ",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He kept quiet …………………….. the argument might stop.",
            "description": "That can indicate the purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "hence",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… he was sick, he stayed at home.",
            "description": "As indicates the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "In case",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}